{
    "subject": "resource/Survival_of_the_Fittest_(song)",
    "predicate": "property/writer",
    "object": "resource/Prodigy_(rapper)",
    "human_readable": "The song 'Survival of the Fittest' was written by Prodigy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9510951638221741,
            "question": "Who wrote the song 'Survival of the Fittest'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8612511157989502,
            "question": "Which song was written by Prodigy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8246638774871826,
            "question": "What is the name of the artist who wrote 'Survival of the Fittest'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6051920652389526,
            "question": "What made 'Survival of the Fittest' a successful song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46105024218559265,
            "question": "What genre is likely associated with the song 'Survival of the Fittest'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3714355230331421,
            "question": "Is 'Survival of the Fittest' considered a classic hip-hop track?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35727041959762573,
            "question": "How did Prodigy's lyrics influence other artists?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3185402452945709,
            "question": "Can you name another popular song by Prodigy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.250606894493103,
            "question": "What are some common themes in Prodigy's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18450391292572021,
            "question": "What era in music history is Prodigy most associated with?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The song 'Survival of the Fittest' was written by Prodigy.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1885_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes in Prodigy's music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1885_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another popular song by Prodigy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1885_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did Prodigy's lyrics influence other artists?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1885_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1885_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1885_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1885_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1885_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1885_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1885_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1885_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1885_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1885_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1885_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Prodigy's verse on \"Survival of The Fittest\" is his magnum opus, and that he is the one who raps about survival in the song. They also quote Complex, which says that they made the beat for \"Survival of the Fittest\", but it does not contradict the statement that Prodigy wrote the song."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about \"Survival of the Fittest,\" a track on which Prodigy is indeed mentioned as one of the artists. Therefore, the statement that the song 'Survival of the Fittest' was written by Prodigy is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}